Jhal Jhal Jhal
500 Good afternoon everyone and modern
experience spinal time ko Ravan Next
question question number four of the day in
totality will be or 164 tak hai so without any
further delay stick only start thought question was
approaching and interaction
kind signal light blinking no
restriction directly only sharing but
from this and degree liya hai are just once again
repeated question so
avot is your negative approaching interaction
and turned into a relaxed signal light
signal light is 100% subscribe now and
pimp tube light tube light appears and C
Dave
scientist famous only after
engineering the artist Doosu Ayub slow
down and you and you will show the weather it is
page directly or not and you will not only give
me the weather or not this page and not indicate
it famous and will continue till the
driver so you will enter it
towards the inter where there is signal and signal light here
So what should you do when you
reach an intersection and there is a signal
or something like that, what should you do
because there is no restriction
there that you should drive at a certain speed or you
cannot drive at a certain speed, there is no such thing
mentioned there, so at the same speed at which you were
driving till now, stop your vehicle and
set it to 'Clock and only Sharing', then you will
reduce your speed, then you will see
that
I am moving forward, is it only and when
you see that it is only then will you
move forward or dip, we continue to indicate you are coming, keep
moving
with your vehicle but at that time keep doing this to
inform the drivers and producers that
you are going there, whichever question you are doing,
Amazing to away end is that
and make should not everybody stay in here,
by this simple step of answering questions
you can do the next question and
answer in this question road Delhi road very  There are a lot of
benefits that
we can see from this question
that if there is any interest and light
there then
what should you do in that situation
and from every such question we
can learn something or the other about
road safety, about traffic rules,
how should our behavior be and so on and
we can bring about changes in these things till August
[Music]
2018, he was approaching the President
scenes page directly from the city's
Holy Copter in sharing notice to-do
and degree continues to indicate that you are coming up
towards the internet
and there is a signal there which you
should like the signal there because
nothing should be told to
you here is the thing page number, nothing has been
told, so you were just
going on scenes till now or you will stop
and you will
quote when the screen light turns green
and seal mode on the way tomorrow and
proceed only after insuring your doubts towards
your jo  The speed is you will slow down
and then you will decide whether it is right
for you to proceed and you will see whether you will
proceed from here or the dip
continuously to indicate the coming forward
but to tell the driver
that you are the question part in the question is the question will the
question das loop
because just by answering a small strip question
you can not be knowing how
you should be in some
situation can you are you 9:00 how we
can make routes this is a basically
school avengers avengers question how
should be driving and wire on road
subscribe because you are watching
about su will start to follow the and when each and every
citizen you will start to
follow the rules and tagged
deputy mayor jaipur road devils pet world
and destroy you at all school saving
lives of mean that people murdered by road
dip Rudraksh subscribe this pressure like
and your  You
can give this to friends and family members and
tell them about this tree. You can answer the questions
with your family and tell them about
this
Ayyappan Satya. How is our question
system that how is it till Everyday Beta Testing
- Everyday Question and to to to the
road to and and traffic challan and that is why
we should
open those note children word quora
Lut Shetty like we have all these questions in this
question that if we are coming on any road
and there is a light and there is a signal then
what should you do light on this
question is of national interest different
topics
piece different questions on how to
your learning with different questions
on average just once again repeated questions while
approaching signal light blinking
[music]
Seems page directly color and only to do do do do do
if you are using
your there it would have been simple then why do you do
and  You will get a lot of fun from this you will get a
lot of Avengers, subscribe to the Road Road The Road
To Rule, it is a
very
famous one, which is also not, you can answer this with the
help of the link description box
and Facebook and YouTube in different ways
and results every day in the results
result website please pickup this
and answers questions so that you can understand everyone who
made this app